Guide to the Amalgamated Transit Union, Local 587 Records
Special Collections, University of Washington Libraries
- Amalgamated Transit Union, Local 587 records, 1941-2012; 1980-2010; 5680-001; 15 cubic feet 17 boxes
  - CITY OF SEATTLE, METRO TRANSIT, AND KING COUNTY METRO MATERIALS, 1930s-2009; SERIES III
    City of Seattle, Metro Transit, and King County Metro Materials is composed of material created by the major bargaining counterparts for the ATU 587.
    - Governmental Charters, Rules, Policies, and Studies Relating to Transportation, 1930s-2002; Subseries A; Subseries A includes materials from governmental organizations like the city of Seattle, Seattle Municipal Street Railway, and Paratransit (MV) Transportation. These materials tend to relate to transportation and transit in the Seattle area, and range from circa 1930s to 2002. This subseries is subdivided, with materials relating to regulations and rules arranged chronologically followed by materials relating to employee retirement, and finally a series of studies.
      - Seattle Municipal Street Railway Transfers, 1930s (Box-folder 10/6)
      - The Charter of the City of Seattle, 1946; 1950 (Box-folder 10/7)
      - City of Seattle Civil Service Law and Rules, 1942; 1948 (Box-folder 10/8)
      - Seattle-King County Transit Service Map, 1979-1980 (Box-folder 10/9)
      - Paratransit (MV) Transportation Employee Handbook and Employment Guidelines, 2002 (Box-folder 10/10)
      - Ordinance Governing the City Employees' Retirement System, 1953 (Box-folder 10/11)
      - Reports of Board of Administration, Seattle City Employees' Retirement System, 1967-1969; 1976 (Box-folder 10/12)
      - Report, "A Transit Plan for the Metropolitan Area, Seattle and King County," 1972 (Box-folder 17)
      - Alaskan Way Viaduct Replacement Project, 2010 Supplemental Draft Environmental Impact Statement Executive Summary, Oct. 2010 (Box-folder 17)
      - Alaskan Way Viaduct Replacement Project, Final Environmental Impact Statement Summary, July 2011 (Box-folder 17)
    - Seattle Transit System Annual Report, 1941-1966; Subseries B
      Subseries B contains copies of the Seattle Transit System Annual Report from many of the years between 1941 and 1966 arranged chronologically.
      - Seattle Transit System Annual Report, 1941; 1944 (Box-folder 10/13)
      - Seattle Transit System Annual Report, 1951; 1952; 1955; 1956 (Box-folder 10/14)
      - Seattle Transit System Annual Report, 1957; 1959; 1963; 1964; 1966 (Box-folder 10/15)
    - King County Metro Bus Driver Handbook, The Book, 1970s-2009; Subseries C
      The Book is the term for the King County Metro Bus Driver Handbook, which is published three times per year. Operators are instructed to read The Book and to keep it with them while driving. Changes to each new edition are generally noted at the front of each book, often in an insert. Some of the inserts have been removed and placed next to the books themselves to prevent damage to the book's spine and cover. This subseries is arranged in chronological order.
      - The Book, Undated, c. 1970s (Box-folder 11/1)
      - The Book, Dec. 1980 (Box-folder 11/2)
      - The Book, Feb. 1981 (Box-folder 11/3)
      - The Book, May 1981 (Box-folder 11/4)
      - The Book, Feb. 1982 (Box-folder 11/5)
      - The Book, June 1982 (Box-folder 11/6)
      - The Book, Sept. 1982 (Box-folder 11/7)
      - The Book, Jan. 1983 (Box-folder 11/8)
      - The Book, June 1983 (Box-folder 11/9)
      - The Book, Sept. 1983 (Box-folder 11/10)
      - The Book, Feb. 1984 (Box-folder 11/11)
      - The Book, June 1984 (Box-folder 11/12)
      - The Book, Sept. 1984 (Box-folder 11/13)
      - The Book, Feb. 1985 (Box-folder 12/1)
      - The Book, June 1985 (Box-folder 12/2)
      - The Book, Sept. 1985 (Box-folder 12/3)
      - The Book, Feb. 1986 (Box-folder 12/4)
      - The Book, June 1986 (Box-folder 12/5)
      - The Book, Sept. 1986 (Box-folder 12/6)
      - The Book, Feb. 1987 (Box-folder 12/7)
      - The Book, June 1987 (Box-folder 12/8)
      - The Book, Sept. 1987 (Box-folder 12/9)
      - The Book, Feb. 1988 (Box-folder 12/10)
      - The Book, June 1988 (Box-folder 12/11)
      - The Book, Sept. 1988 (Box-folder 12/12)
      - The Book, Feb. 1989 (Box-folder 12/13)
      - The Book, June 1989 (Box-folder 12/14)
      - The Book, Sept. 1989 (Box-folder 12/15)
      - The Book, Feb. 1990 (Box-folder 12/16)
      - The Book, June 1990 (Box-folder 12/17)
      - The Book, Sept. 1990 (Box-folder 12/18)
      - The Book, Feb. 1991 (Box-folder 13/1)
      - The Book, June 1991 (Box-folder 13/2)
      - The Book, Sept. 1991 (Box-folder 13/3)
      - The Book, Feb. 1992 (Box-folder 13/4)
      - The Book, June 1992 (Box-folder 13/5)
      - The Book, Aug. 1992 (Box-folder 13/6)
      - The Book, Feb. 1993 (Box-folder 13/7)
      - The Book, June 1993 (Box-folder 13/8)
      - The Book, Aug. 1993 (Box-folder 13/9)
      - The Book, Feb. 1994 (Box-folder 13/10)
      - The Book, June 1994 (Box-folder 13/11)
      - The Book, Sept. 1994 (Box-folder 13/12)
      - The Book, Feb. 1995 (Box-folder 13/13)
      - The Book, June 1995 (Box-folder 13/14)
      - The Book, Sept. 1995 (Box-folder 13/15)
      - The Book, Feb. 1996 (Box-folder 13/16)
      - The Book, June 1996 (Box-folder 13/17)
      - The Book, Sept. 1996 (Box-folder 13/18)
      - The Book, Feb. 1997 (Box-folder 14/1)
      - The Book, June 1997 (Box-folder 14/2)
      - The Book, Sept. 1997 (Box-folder 14/3)
      - The Book, Feb. 1998 (Box-folder 14/4)
      - The Book, June 1998 (Box-folder 14/5)
      - The Book, Sept. 1998 (Box-folder 14/6)
      - The Book, Feb. 1999 (Box-folder 14/7)
      - The Book, June 1999 (Box-folder 14/8)
      - The Book, Sept. 1999 (Box-folder 14/9)
      - The Book, Feb. 2000 (Box-folder 14/10)
      - The Book, June 2000 (Box-folder 14/11)
      - The Book, Sept. 2000 (Box-folder 14/12)
      - The Book, June 2001 (Box-folder 14/13)
      - The Book, Sept. 2001 (Box-folder 14/14)
      - The Book, Feb. 2002 (Box-folder 14/15)
      - The Book, June 2002 (Box-folder 14/16)
      - The Book, Sept. 2002 (Box-folder 14/17)
      - The Book, Feb. 2003 (Box-folder 15/1)
      - The Book, June 2003 (Box-folder 15/2)
      - The Book, Sept. 2003 (Box-folder 15/3)
      - The Book, Feb. 2004 (Box-folder 15/4)
      - The Book, June 2004 (Box-folder 15/5)
      - The Book, Sept. 2004 (Box-folder 15/6)
      - The Book, Feb. 2005 (Box-folder 15/7)
      - The Book, June 2005 (Box-folder 15/8)
      - The Book, Sept. 2005 (Box-folder 15/9)
      - The Book, Feb. 2006 (Box-folder 15/10)
      - The Book, June 2006 (Box-folder 15/11)
      - The Book, Sept. 2006 (Box-folder 15/12)
      - The Book, June 2007 (Box-folder 15/13)
      - The Book, Sept. 2007 (Box-folder 15/14)
      - The Book, Feb. 2008 (Box-folder 15/15)
      - The Book, June 2008 (Box-folder 15/16)
      - The Book, Sept. 2008 (Box-folder 15/17)
      - The Book, Feb. 2009 (Box-folder 15/18)
    - Other Seattle Metro and King County Metro Publications, 1959-1987; Subseries D
      This subseries is composed of newsletters, primarily those produced by the Seattle Transit System or Seattle Metro. The first section of newsletters, Transit Talk, was produced by the Seattle Transit System, and ranges from 1943 to 1948. The second section is Transit News, a newsletter put out by Seattle Metro. The third section consists of publications put out by other governmental transit organizations that are bargaining partners with ATU 587.
      - Part 1: Transit Talk, Aug. 1943-1948 (Box-folder 2/22-35)
        - Transit Talk Aug. 1943 (Box-folder 2/22)
        - Transit Talk Jan.-June 1944 (Box-folder 2/23)
        - Transit Talk July-Dec. 1944 (Box-folder 2/24)
        - Transit Talk Jan.-June 1945 (Box-folder 2/25)
        - Transit Talk July-Dec. 1945 (Box-folder 2/26)
        - Transit Talk Jan.-June 1946 (Box-folder 2/27)
        - Transit Talk July-Dec. 1946 (Box-folder 2/28)
        - Transit Talk Jan.-June 1947 (Box-folder 2/29)
        - Transit Talk July-Sept. 1947, 0July-Sept. 1947 (Box-folder 2/30)
        - Transit Talk Mid-Winter Issue 1947 (Box-folder 2/31)
        - Transit Talk March 1948 (Box-folder 2/32)
        - Transit Talk April 1948 (Box-folder 2/33)
        - Transit Talk Mid-Year 1948 (Box-folder 2/34)
        - Transit Talk Oct. 1948 (Box-folder 2/35)
      - Part 2: Transit News, 1959-1982 (Box-folder 10/16-17)
        - Transit News, Jan. 1959; Aug. 1959-Dec. 1959 (Box-folder 10/16)
        - Transit News, 1961-1982 (Box-folder 10/17)
      - Part 3: Other Publications, 1974-1987 (Box-folder 10/18-20)
        - Clearwater Transit Times, 1974-1983 (Box-folder 10/18)
        - The Insider, 1984; 1987 (Box-folder 10/19)
        - King County Metro, Resolving Conflict, A Pocket Guide, Undated (Box-folder 10/20)
  - MATERIALS FROM OTHER ATU LOCAL UNIONS AND TRANSIT ORGANIZATIONS OUTSIDE OF THE SEATTLE AREA, 1990-1993; SERIES IV
    This series is arranged chronologically.
    This series consists of materials produced by other local unions: ATU 583 in Edmonton, ATU 843 in Bellingham, and the Portland Tri-Met transit organization.
    - Local Colour, A Commemoration of the 75th Anniversary of ATU 583, 1990 (Box-folder 10/3)
    - ATU 843 Bellingham 75th Anniversary Retrospective, 1993 (Box-folder 10/4)
    - Tri-Met 20th Anniversary Portland, Oregon, 1990 (Box-folder 10/5)
  - MATERIALS FROM AFFILIATED LABOR ORGANIZATIONS, 1957-1995; SERIES V
    This series is divided into subseries based on creator, then arranged chronologically within the subseries.
    Materials from Affiliated Labor Organizations contains documents created by other labor-related organizations divided into sections based on originator.
    - Materials from the AFL-CIO, 1976-1991; Subseries A
      This subseries consists of resolutions from AFL-CIO conventions and instructional materials put out by the AFL-CIO.
      - AFL-CIO Resolutions, 18th Convention, 1989 (Box-folder 10/21)
      - AFL-CIO Resolutions, 19th Convention, 1991 (Box-folder 10/22)
      - AFL-CIO Report, 19th Convention, 1991 (Box-folder 10/23)
      - AFL-CIO Manual for Shop Stewards, circa 1986 (Box-folder 10/24)
      - AFL-CIO How to Run a Union Meeting, 1976 (Box-folder 10/25)
      - Workers' Memorial Day Ribbon, Undated (Box-folder 10/26)
    - Materials from the Washington State Labor Council, 1984-1988; Subseries B
      This subseries contains proceedings from the Washington State Labor Council (WSLC) conventions from 1984-1988, arranged chronologically.
      - Washington State Labor Council 1984 Convention Proceedings (Box-folder 10/27)
      - Washington State Labor Council 1986 Convention Proceedings (Box-folder 10/28)
      - Washington State Labor Council 1988 Convention Proceedings (Box-folder 10/29)
    - Union Labor Report, Bureau of National Affairs, 1993-1995; Subseries C
      This subseries contains the Union Labor Reports from 1993, 1994, and 1995, produced by the Bureau of National Affairs.
      - Union Labor Report, 1993-1995 (Box-folder 10/30-10/33)
    - Materials from Other Labor Organizations, 1957-1982; Subseries D
      This subseries includes documents from the Port Angeles Central Labor Council, King County Labor Council, International Union of Electrical, Radio, and Machine Workers, a Washington State Worker Rights Complaint, and labor-inspired calendars.
      - Port Angeles Central Labor Council, Constitution and By-Laws, 1957 (Box-folder 10/34)
      - Constitution and By-Laws of the King County Labor Council, 1982 (Box-folder 10/35)
      - National Apprenticeship and Training Standards for the International Union of Electrical, Radio, and Machine Workers (IUE), 1976 (Box-folder 10/36)
      - Washington State Worker Rights Complaint, Undated (Box-folder 10/37)
      - Strength Grace Courage: Rosie's Legacy Calendar 2008, 2007; Labor activist Irene Hull is profiled in this calendar, and signed her photo. A letter from Hull accompanies the calendar. (Box-folder 10/38)
      - Labor History Calendar 2012, 2011 (Box-folder 10/39)
- Amalgamated Transit Union, Local 587 records, 1999-2012; 5680-002; 2 cubic feet (2 boxes) plus 1 oversize folder
  ATU publications, constitution and general bylaws, collective bargaining agreements, route maps, ATU 587 Centennial photos and ephemera; memorobilia, patches, and pins; union election materials. ATU International convention proceedings, collective bargaining agreements of other ATU locals.
  Donor: Pamela Hoang, Amalgamated Transit Workers, Local 587, April 12, 2013.
  - AMALGAMATED TRANSIT UNION PUBLICATIONS, 2012; SERIES I (Box-folder 1/1)
    - Amalgamated Transit Untion Local 587 News Review (s), 2012 (Box-folder 1/1)
  - AMALGAMATED TRANSIT CONSTITUTION AND GENERAL LAWS, 2004; SERIES II (Box-folder 1/2)
    - Constitution and General Laws as amended 2004 (Box-folder 1/2)
  - COLLECTIVE BARGAINING AGREEMENTS, 2008-2014; SERIES III (Box-folder 1/3-1/9)
    - Collective Bargaining Agreement between Amalgamated Transit Union and King County Addendum for Rail Employees, exp 2010 (Box-folder 1/3)
    - Collective Bargaining Agreement between Amalgamated Transit Union and Jefferson Transit Authority, exp 2013, 2011-2013 (Box-folder 1/4)
    - Collective Bargaining Agreement between Amalgamated Transit Union and First Transit, Inc. Call Center, exp 2014, 2010-2014 (Box-folder 1/5)
    - Collective Bargaining Agreement between Amalgamated Transit Union and Clallam Transit System, Terms and Conditions for Paratransit Employees, exp 2012 (Box-folder 1/6)
    - Collective Bargaining Agreement between Amalgamated Transit Union and Paratransit Services, exp 2012, 2010-2012 (Box-folder 1/7)
    - Collective Bargaining Agreement between Amalgamated Transit Union and Clallam Transit System, exp 2014, 2010-2014 (Box-folder 1/8)
    - Collective Bargaining Agreement between Amalgamated Transit Union and Seattle Personal Transit, exp 2009, 2008-2009 (Box-folder 1/9)
  - KING COUNTY ROUTE BOOKS, 2012-2013; SERIES IV (Box-folder 1/10-1/11)
    - Route Book Transit Routes, exp 2012, King County (Box-folder 1/10)
    - Route Book Transit Routes, exp 2013, King County, 2012-2013 (Box-folder 1/11)
  - DIRECTORIES, 2011; SERIES V (Box-folder 1/12)
    - Amalgamated Transit Union 2011 Local Union Directory (Box-folder 1/12)
  - CONVENTION MATERIALS, 2004; SERIES VI (Box-folder 1/13-1/16)
    - Amalgamated Transit Union Fifty Fourth Convention - Proceedings: Las Vegas, NV September 13-17, 2004 (Box-folder 1/13)
    - Amalgamated Transit Union Fifty Fourth Convention - International Reports: Las Vegas, NV September 13-17, 2004 (Box-folder 1/14)
    - Amalgamated Transit Union Fifty Fourth Convention - Programs: Las Vegas, NV September 13-17, 2004 (Box-folder 1/15)
    - Amalgamated Transit Union Fifty Fourth Convention - Resolutions: Las Vegas, NV September 13-17, 2004 (Box-folder 1/16)
  - LABOR PUBLICATION, 2000; SERIES VII (Box-folder 1/17)
    - Labor's Heritage, Vol. 11/No. 1 Quarterly of the George Meany Memorial Archives, 2000 (Box-folder 1/17)
  - AMALGAMATED TRANSIT UNION LOCAL 113, TORONTO CANADA 100TH ANNIVERSARY MATERIALS, 1999; SERIES VIII (Box-folder 1/18)
    - Amalgamated Transit Union Local 113 Toronto Canada - 100th Aniversary 1899-1999 Booklet (Box-folder 1/18)
  - CENTENNIAL MATERIALS, AMALGAMATED TRANSIT UNION LOCAL 587, 2012; SERIES IX (Box-folder 1/19)
    - Amalgamated Transit Union Local 587 Centennial 2012: (Pictures, Invitation, centennial program agenda, Amalgamated Association of Street and Electric Railway Employees of America charter, Remarks by County Council Co-Chair Jane Hague, Message from King County Council member Kathy Lambert, Greetings from the Governor, Seattle Local 587 100th Anniversary Address, Metropolitan King County Council Recognition, and DVD (Amalgamated Transit Union, Local 587, 100th Anniversary) (Box-folder 1/19)
  - LOCAL ELECTION MATERIALS, AMALGAMATED TRANSIT UNION LOCAL 587, 1997, 2003, 2009-2012; SERIES X (Box-folder 1/20)
    - Amalgamated Transit Union Local 587 Elections Materials: Don MacAdam 2012 Flyer, Kenny McCormick 2012 Flyer, Kermit Gipson 2012 Flyer, Bruce Tiebout 2012 Flyer, Verita Alexander 2012 Flyer, Paul Bachtel 2012 button, Local 587 2012 Officer Elections Pamphlet, Local 587 2003 Officer Elections Voters Pamphlet, Local 587 2006 Officer Elections Pamphlet, Local 587 2009 Officer Elections Pamphlet, Local 587 1997 Voters Pamphlet, 1997, 2003, 2009-2012 (Box-folder 1/20)
  - EPHEMERA, Undated, 1983, 2012; SERIES XI (Box-folder 1/21-1/23)
    - MV Access/140 jobs "lost" arm strap, Amalgamated Transit Union Local 587 patch, Public Transit National Day of Action April 4, 2012 sticker, Amalgamated Transit Union "ATU for Obama/Biden" button, Undated-2012 (Box-folder 1/21)
    - Pins (City of Seattle, Local 583 Calgary, and Amalgamated Transit Union: COPE, Local 587, Local 587 Officer, Local 587 Steward, 100th Anniversary) and Medallion (Amalgamated Transit Union COPE, The Voice of Transit Workers), Undated-1983 (Box-folder 1/22)
    - DVD: Amalgamated Transit Union, Local 587, Executive Board (Contains 114 images of the Executive Board, as a group and individually), 2012 (Box-folder 1/23)
  - AMALGAMATED TRANSIT UNION CONSTITUTION AND HANDBOOK, 1981, 1983, 1986, 2005; SERIES XII (Box-folder 2/1-2/5)
    - Constitution and General Laws Amalgamated Transit Union affliliated with American Federation of Labor-Congress of Industrial Organizations and Canadian Labor Congress, 1981 (Box-folder 2/1)
    - Constitution and General Laws Amalgamated Transit Union affliliated with American Federation of Labor-Congress of Industrial Organizations and Canadian Labor Congress, 1983 (Box-folder 2/2)
    - Constitution and General Laws Amalgamated Transit Union affliliated with American Federation of Labor-Congress of Industrial Organizations and Canadian Labor Congress, 1986 (Box-folder 2/3)
    - The 587 Handbook: A Guide to Our Union, Amalgamated Transit Union Local 587, Seattle Washington, 1986 (Box-folder 2/4)
    - The 587 Handbook: A Guide to Our Union and History Into the King County Metro Era, Amalgamated Transit Union Local 587, Seattle Washington, 2005 (Box-folder 2/5)
  - LABOR AGREEMENTS, 1973-2014; SERIES XIII (Box-folder 2/6-2/31)
    - Agreement by and between Clallam Transit Systems and Amalgamated Transit Union, Local 587, 2001-2003 (Box-folder 2/6)
    - Agreement between Amalgamated Transit Union, Local 587 and Clallam Transit System, 2004-2006 (Box-folder 2/7)
    - Labor agreement between Clallam Transit System and Amalgamated Transit Union, Local 587, 2010-2014 (Box-folder 2/8)
    - Labor agreement between Clallam Transit System and Amalgamated Transit Union, Local 587, Terms and conditions of employment for paratransit employees, 2011-2012 (Box-folder 2/9)
    - Agreement by and between Jefferson Transit Authority and the Amalgamated Transit Union, Local 587, 2002-2004 (Box-folder 2/10)
    - Agreement between Amalgamated Transit Union, Local 587 and Jefferson Transit Authority, 2005-2007 (Box-folder 2/11)
    - Agreement between Amalgamated Transit Union, Local 587 and Jefferson Transit Authority, 2008-2010 (Box-folder 2/12)
    - Agreement by and between Municipality of Metro Seattle and Amalgamated Transit Union, Division No. 587, 1973 (Box-folder 2/13)
    - Agreement by and betweeen Muncipality of Metro Seattle and Amalgamated Transit Union, Division No. 587, 1981-1984 (Box-folder 2/14)
    - Agreement by and betweeen Muncipality of Metro Seattle and Amalgamated Transit Union, Division No. 587, 1984-1987 (Box-folder 2/15)
    - Agreement by and betweeen Muncipality of Metro Seattle and Amalgamated Transit Union, Local 587, 1987-1990 (Box-folder 2/16)
    - Agreement between Amalgamated Transit Union, Local 587 and MV public Transportation, Inc. South Park, 2004-2007 (Box-folder 2/17)
    - Labor agreement by and between MV Transportation and Amalgamated Transit Union, Local 587, AFL-CIO, Seattle Washington, 2007 (Box-folder 2/18)
    - Labor agreement between Amalgamated Transit Union, Local 587, AFL-CIO and Paratransit Services, 2004-2006 (Box-folder 2/19)
    - Labor agreement between Paratransit Services and Amalgamated Transit Union, Local 587, 2007-2009 (Box-folder 2/20)
    - Agreement by and between the Seattle Personal Transit and the Amalgamated Transit Union, Local 587, 2002-2005 (Box-folder 2/21)
    - Labor agreement by and between Amalgamated Transit Untion, Local 587 and Seattle Personal Transit, 2005-2008 (Box-folder 2/22)
    - Labor agreement by and between Amalgamated Transit Untion, Local 587 and Seattle Personal Transit, 2008-2009 (Box-folder 2/23)
    - Labor agreement by and between Amalgamated Transit Untion, Local 587 and Seattle Personal Transit, 2009-2012 (Box-folder 2/24)
    - Agreement by and between Amalgamated Transit Union, Local 587 and King Country Metro Transit, 1995-1998 (Box-folder 2/25)
    - Agreement by and between Amalgamated Transit Union, Local 587 and King Country Metro Transit, 1998-2001 (Box-folder 2/26)
    - Agreement by and between Amalgamated Transit Union, Local 587 and King Country Metro Transit, 2004-2007 (Box-folder 2/27)
    - Agreement by and between Amalgamated Transit Union, Local 587 and King Country Metro Transit, 2010 (Box-folder 2/28)
    - Agreement between Amalgamated Transit Union, Local 587 and King Country Metro Transit, Addendum - Terms and Conditions of Employment for Rail Employees, 2010 (Box-folder 2/29)
    - Agreement by and between Amalgamated Transit Union, Local 587 and King Country Metro Transit, 2013 (Box-folder 2/30)
    - Exhibit D, Agreement between Amalgamated Transit Union, Local 587 and King Country Metro Transit, Terms and Conditions of Employment for Rail Employees, 2013 (Box-folder 2/31)
  - EPHEMERA, 1970-2012; SERIES XIV (Box-folder 2/32-2/38)
    - Pins (Amalgamated Transit Union, Local 587, Romanian Council) and button (100 Years of Transit, Take Your Seat in History 1884-1984), 1984-2002 (Box-folder 2/32)
    - Decal: Amalgamated Transit Union, Organized Sept. 15, 1892: This Vehicle Operated and Maintained by Union Members, Undated (Box-folder 2/33)
    - Medallion, gold-plated in plastic clamshell case, "Downtown Seattle Transit Tunnel, Metro, In Recognition & Appreciation of Your Contribution", 1990 (Box-folder 2/34)
    - Seattle Trolley Coaches by Harre W. Demoro,, Interurban magazine Special 54, Volume 27, Number 2, 1970 (Box-folder 2/35)
    - DVD: Amalgamated Transit Union, Local 587, 100th Anniversary, Copy 2 (Contains 700 pictures of attendees, band, and presenters at Centennial celebration - no names are listed.), 2012 (Box-folder 2/36)
    - Photographs/Photo Prints: Local Hero Frederick Coats & P/T Rick (January 1993), Joe Trautman OP Trolley Laurelhurst, Admin Day (2011 Photographer: Verita), unlabeled/undated print of large group of people in Seattle, 1993-2011 (Box-folder 2/37)
    - King County Metro's Operators of the Year. Poster print - Oversized, 1979-2010 (Box-folder Oversize Folder)
- Amalgamated Transit Union, Local 587 records, 1982-2015; 5680-003; 6.84 cubic feet (6 boxes)
  ATU international union and Local 587 publications including "ATU 587 News Review"; ATU 587 collective bargaining agreements. King County Metro Transit publications including route maps, and The book: transit operating instructions --a manual for transit drivers in the King County transit system, 1982-2010. ATU 587 photos and ephemera; memorobilia, patches, and pins.
- Amalgamated Transit Union, Local 587 records, 1948-2019; 5680-004; 4.27 cubic feet (3 boxes and 1 tube) and 1 OS folder
  Office files, union and politics-related ephemera, and photographs and flyers from ATU 587 events.
  No restrictions on access.
  - Amalgamated Transit Union Application for Funeral Benefit, Undated (Box-folder 1/1)